{
    "subject": "Catherine_de'_Medici",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Henry_II_of_France",
    "human_readable": "Catherine de' Medici is married to Henry II of France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8697775602340698,
            "question": "Who was Catherine de' Medici married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628385066986084,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Henry II and Catherine de' Medici?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8255011439323425,
            "question": "Who was the king of France when Catherine de' Medici married him?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8120704889297485,
            "question": "To whom did Catherine de' Medici have a marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7480006217956543,
            "question": "Can you name the husband of Catherine de' Medici?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7290493845939636,
            "question": "Who was the king that Catherine de' Medici married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696436405181885,
            "question": "What is the name of Catherine de' Medici's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6609531044960022,
            "question": "What is the title of Catherine de' Medici's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309295892715454,
            "question": "With whom was Catherine de' Medici in a marital union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6083716750144958,
            "question": "What historical figure did Catherine de' Medici marry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Catherine de' Medici is married to Henry II of France.",
            "html": "yago_21093_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=With whom was Catherine de' Medici in a marital union?",
            "html": "yago_21093_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of Catherine de' Medici's husband?",
            "html": "yago_21093_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Catherine de' Medici's husband?",
            "html": "yago_21093_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21093_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate whether the statement \"Catherine de' Medici is married to Henry II of France\" is supported by the documents.\n\nThe answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because there are multiple documents that mention Catherine de' Medici being married to King Henry II of France. For example, in the first document, it says \"Catherine de Medici was aged twenty-four and had been married to Henry II of France for ten years...\", and in the second document, it explicitly states that she was Queen consort of France from 1547 until 1559, as the wife of King Henry II of France."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Catherine de\u2019 Medici\u2019s marriage to King Henry II of France, which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}